

JONATHAN CAUDRON

DEVELOPPER

CONTACT

+33768666191

jonathan_caudron@ens.univ-artois.fr

39 Résidence Le Titien 62800. Liévin

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

PHP

JAVA

PYTHON

SOFTWARES

FIGMA, VS CODE, PYCHARM, PHPSTORM, INTELLIJ, VISUAL STUDIO

PROFIL

Je m'appelle Jonathan Caudron, depuis mes 10 ans j'ai développé une passion dans le développement en général, pendant mon temps libre j'ai pu améliorer mes compétences. Je sais créer des designs et créer des projets dans différents langages.

EXPERIENCE

2020-2021 Projet Tutoré S1

University of Artois - IUT de Lens

My name is Jonathan Caudron, since I was 10 I have developed a passion for development in general, in my free time I have been able to improve my skills. I know how to create designs and create projects in different languages.

2018-2020 Nelastia

Nelastia

I participated in the creation of a "Minecraft" game server, mainly developed in Java and linked to a MySQL database for user data. This project helped me in learning and deepening Java language and SQL.

2017-2018 ICN (HTML)

Henri Darras High School (Liévin)

I participated in the creation of a Berck kite themed site in a group of two, using mainly HTML, CSS and JavaScript, using the Bootstrap library.

EDUCATION

2020-2021 DUT Info

University of Artois – IUT de Lens

2017-2020 BAC STI2D

Henri Darras High School (Liévin)